Guide to the Sarah G. Jacobson Papers MSS.157
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Accretion 2008 - Series IV: Professional Projects
  - Subseries J: Media Originals
    - "Oh the Ladies" Ep. 2 - Film Front Interview, Undated (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0325)
    - "Women Director's Summit, 50/50's Meeting", Undated (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0388)
    - 50/50 Part II / "Our First Time," "Cowboy Jesus Fork" by Suki Hawley, Undated (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0389)
    - 50/50 Show "My First Time" [1] "Discharge" - Jamie Babbitt [2] "Sleep" - Helen Stickler [3] "Mary in the Water" - Tamra Davis [4] "The Slap" - Tamara Hernandez [5] "Sweet Miss The Disco Years" - Sarah Jacobson [6] "The Air Globes" - Patricia Cardoso [7] "How to Make an Oliver Stone Movie" - Mary Harron, Undated (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0390)
    - "Trackers - Summer Concert Safety", Undated (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0327)
    - "DV 3 I Trackers - Hellstock 8/99, Suki Hawley, Tonya Lewis #1, producer Sarah Jacobson", 1999 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0420)
    - "DV 4 II Trackers - Hellstock 8/99, Tanya Lewis #2, producer Sarah Jacobson", 1999 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0421)
    - "DV 5 Intern I, Concert 6/9/00", 2000 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0395)
    - "DV 6 Intern II, Simone & Sharon Concert Safety", Undated (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0396)
    - "Hellstock #1, Sarah & Cindy 8/99", 1999 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0422)
    - "Hellstock #2, Sarah & Cindy 8/99", 1999 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0423)
    - "Hellstock, Cynthia, Cindy 8/99", 1999 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0424)
    - "Hellstock, Jessica, Cynthia 8/99", 1999 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0425)
    - "Summer Concert Safety Master", Undated (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0394)
      Format: DVCam, Donated Element
    - "Woodstock", Undated (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0407)
    - "Woodstock 2", Undated (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0408)
    - "DV 14 Woodstock TV", Undated (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0409)
    - "RI: Phantom Planet Segments", Undated (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0367)
    - "RI: Phantom Planet", Undated (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0393)
    - "Phunky Bitches #1 5/21/00", 2000 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0386)
    - "Phunky Bitches #2 5/21/00", 2000 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0387)
    - "DV 16 Phunky Bitch B-Roll 6/20/00" (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0385)
    - "Sarah's Pseudo Reel" - [1] Cecil B. Demented [2] Blackout Books [3] Toys in Babeland [4] Radical Cheerleaders, Undated; cuid40995 (Box 29, Dvcam ID: 157.0398)
    - "Third Wave B-roll", Undated (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0440)
    - "3rd Wave - Brdl, Esther Dancing, Carnival w/Scott, Boss Hog, Movie Screening Girl Int, Dictionary", Undated (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0439)
    - "Oxygen Etc. B-Roll Tape A" - [1] Oxygen Office [2] Lots of Black [3] Bluestockings [4] Mixfest [5] Editing [6] Yo Yo Girl [7] Mixfest (Bluestockings Vag. Creme Davis Mr. Lady) 11/99, 1999 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0441)
    - "S26 - Studio Shot by Kirsten", Undated (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0426)
    - "S27" - [1] Belly Dancers [2] Club Going [3] No More Prisons Talk, Undated (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0416)
    - "S28" - No More Prisons Talk, Pt. 2, Undated (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0417)
    - "Columbia Tape 1 TTV", Undated (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0418)
    - "Columbia Tape 2 TTV", Undated (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0419)
    - "CUFF #1 Animal Charm Lakeview 8/99", 1999 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0410)
    - "CUFF #2 Interview Park 8/99", 1999 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0411)
    - "CUFF #3 Bowling 8/16/99", 1999 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0412)
    - "CUFF #4 Bowling, Airport 8/99", 1999 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0413)
    - "Sarah's Reel Master 2002" [EMPTY] (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0399)
      This is an empty Mini DV Box, it contains the following notation: "w/ Red Aunts Music, Cecil B. Demented, Phantom Planet, Adam the Tastemaker, Summer Concert Safety, Stains"
    - "Sarah's Reel 2002" - [1] Cecil B. Demented [2] Phantom Planet [3] Adam the Tastemaker [3] Summer Concert Safety [4] Making of the Stains (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0400)
      TRT: 00:08:00
    - "Sarah's Reel 2002 Master 2/21/02" - "w/ Red Aunts Music, Cecil B. Demented, Phantom Planet, Adam, Summer Concert, Stains (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0401)
    - "Cecil B. Demented 8/9/00", 2000 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0403)
    - "Sarah's 02 Reel" - [1] Yo yo [2] NYUFF [3] ABC No Rio [4] Audra / ISW [5] Blue Stockings [6] Building Studio [7] 3rd Wave [8] Knitting, 2002; ID: 157.0414 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0414)
    - "Sarah's '02 Stuff #2" - [1] Tibet [2] Take Back the Decks [3] Circus [4] Pepper Steppers [5] Graffitti [6] Guerilla Girls, 2002; ID: 157.0415 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0415)
    - "TM: Adam", Undated; ID: 157.0404 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0404)
      TRT: 00:40:00
    - "TM: Adam, Shana, Tape 2", Undated; ID: 157.0405 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0405)
      TRT: 00:30:00
    - "Reel Master" - [1] John Waters [2] Crowd Surfing [3] The Stains [4] Take Back the Decks, Undated; ID: 157.0406 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0406)
    - "#1 Radical Cheerleaders", Undated; ID: 157.0427 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0427)
    - "#2 Radical Cheerleaders", 2000; ID: 157.0428 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0428)
    - "BBW / Apartment Before Ladyfest Chicago - Mos Interview, Lady Superstars", Undated; ID: 157.0437 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0437)
    - "DV 8 Ladyfest Chicago - Weird Band, Radical Cheerlead, Evil Beaver, My Press Speech", Undated; ID: 157.0438 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0438)
      The case label contains the following notation: "DV 8, Interviews + B Roll, 311 + No Doubt" while the tape inside reads "Ladyfest Chicago."
    - "Letterman Marquee 11/20/02", ID: 157.0442 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0442)
    - "DV 15 Self Defense / Logos", ID: 157.0443 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0443)
    - "Ann Powers #1 9/20/99 NY", 1999; ID: 157.0444 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0444)
    - "Trackers 9/99, Ann Powers #2, Galen NOW #1, producer Sarah Jacobson", 1999; ID: 157.0445 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0445)
    - "Galen NOW 9/99", 1999; ID: 157.0446 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0446)
    - "Anton in Mpls 2/01", 2001; ID: 157.0447 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0447)
    - "David Friedman, Steve Buschemi! LA Trip 4/00", 2000; ID: 157.0448 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0448)
    - "Gillian Armstrong, AIDS Test 10/99 SF", 1999; ID: 157.0449 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0449)
    - "Gilman Show, Sell More Books Jack Stevenson, CW, Freeway 2 SF 10/99", 1999; ID: 157.0450 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0450)
    - "Jim Jarmusch, My Rock Debut CBGBs - Basement DIY Fest 2/21/01", 2001; ID: 157.0451 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0451)
    - "Sarah St. Vincent 12/31/2003", ID: 157.0452 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0452)
    - "Thurston Gary, Got a Job Dave Markey 9/23/99 NY", 1999; ID: 157.0453 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0453)
    - "Willie Brown Nellie 10/6/99 SF", 1999; ID: 157.0454 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0454)
    - "Baltimore FF '00, Will at Waiting Brooklyn Show", 2000; ID: 157.0457 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0457)
    - "IKON Modeling Footage", Undated; ID: 157.0460 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0460)
    - "NY - CMJ Bratmobile, Don Letts Gary 9/99", 1999; ID: 157.0463 (Box 29, Media ID: 157.0463)
- Accretion 2008 - Series V: Miscellaneous Media Originals
  Conditions Governing Use
  This series includes donated media elements. Access copies may not be available for consultation, please ask a Fales archivist.
  - Subseries A: Audio Recordings
    - "Paula Rambles - This Side", Undated; ID: 157.0483 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0483)
    - "Please Forward to Sarah, Jan '99, WSIA FM, Michael Horan III", 1999; ID: 157.0484 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0484)
    - "Annie - Sarah com. pk.", Undated; ID: 157.0485 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0485)
    - "Sarah on the Alex Bennett Show", Undated; ID: 157.0486 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0486)
    - "Sarah - Beth Friend - Full Program, [Side A] KNOW Interview, [Side B] A Rainbow Path - Kay Gardner, Music by Melissa Verdio", 1990; ID: 157.0487 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0487)
    - "KROQ Station Wagon Productions", Undated; ID: 157.0491 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0491)
    - "Half Moon Bay" KT66/4, Undated; ID: 157.0493 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0493)
      TRT: 00:03:30
    - "Bat Mitzvah Sarah, Compliments of Temple Israel Men's Club", Undated; ID: 157.0494 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0494)
    - "Master Phil, Jam", Undated; ID: 157.0495 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0495)
    - "Sarah Jacobson / Rev 105, Mpls, MN", Undated; ID: 157.0498 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0498)
    - "Film Close-Ups, Apr. 1", No Year; ID: 157.0499 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0499)
  - Subseries C: Video Recordings, Independent Media
    - Godass by Esther Bell, 2000; ID: 157.0340 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0340)
    - The Films of Jeff Krulik and Friends, Undated; ID: 157.0342 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0342)
    - The Litter Box by George Kuchar, 1997; ID: 157.0343 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0343)
    - Metropolitan Monologues by George Kuchar, 2000; ID: 157.0344 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0344)
    - Munchkins of Melody Manor by George Kuchar, Undated; ID: 157.0345 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0345)
    - Metallica Drummer, Undated; ID: 157.0346 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0346)
    - "She Thing" The Judy Spots, Director: S. Benning, Producer: E. Subrin, Undated; ID: 157.0350 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0350)
    - "3 Student Films" - [1] Shaded [2] Thurs. Kool-Aid [3] Ben, Ali, Allison, Undated; ID: 157.0352 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0352)
  - Subseries D: Video Recording (VHS), Other - Originals
    - "PXL - Art School Chicks Save Rock + Roll", Undated; ID: 157.0318 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0318)
    - "Roller Skating PXL", Undated; ID: 157.0319 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0319)
    - "Rough Pixel", Undated; ID: 157.0320 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0320)
    - "Transferred PXL - Vol II", Undated; ID: 157.0321 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0321)
    - "White Apache PXL", Undated; ID: 157.0322 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0322)
    - "Riefenstahl Recorded, Julie's, MTV Video Music Awards", Undated; ID: 157.0323 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0323)
    - "90210 - Just, Art School Chicks - None", Undated; ID: 157.0324 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0324)
    - "Sarah, Katie & Ali, Recorded TV Show First, (1987? 1989)", ID: 157.0326 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0326)
    - "Ally's Party Tape", Undated; ID: 157.0329 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0329)
    - "Apartment, Madison 1991, Sarah Raps", ID: 157.0330 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0330)
    - "Brighton Beach Memoirs, Edina High School, April 13-15, 1989", ID: 157.0331 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0331)
    - "Brit, Ally & Sarah Apr. 23, 1988", ID: 157.0332 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0332)
    - "(Blank) Sarah's Party, July '89 -Flashdancing, -Jen Reeves & Me, -Cory's Apt in NY (Boring)", 1989; ID: 157.0333 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0333)
    - "To: Sarah, From: Nardwvar, 'My life story...so far!'", Undated; ID: 157.0334 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0334)
    - "Fisher Price Tape, Filming SK 1992", ID: 157.0335 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0335)
    - "(Blank) Jenny Anderson, Joy Hagen, Sarah Jacobson, hour 6", Undated; ID: 157.0336 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0336)
    - "E-Day! Big Titles Chevy Chase", Undated; ID: 157.0337 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0337)
      TRT: 00:03:00
    - "Dogs in Space", Undated; ID: 157.0338 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0338)
    - "No Alternative Girls, Sonic Youth, Vida Loca, Luscious Jackson - Tamra", Undated; ID: 157.0348 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0348)
    - "South w/ Charles, McAllister Apt., Mount Tam", Undated; ID: 157.0351 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0351)
    - "White River Apache Vol. 1", Undated; ID: 157.0353 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0353)
    - "#3 Radical / Rally 1", Undated; ID: 157.0429 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0429)
    - "DV 4 Rally 2 [No Sound]", Undated; ID: 157.0430 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0430)
    - "State Fair Reunion 8/99", 1999; ID: 157.0433 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0433)
    - "Mpls Grumpy's State Fair 8/99", 1999; ID: 157.0434 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0434)
    - "Anton El Mack, Reunion After Party 8/99", 1999; ID: 157.0436 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0436)
    - "Album Covers 2000", ID: 157.0455 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0455)
    - "Bra Shopping PXL Tape", Undated; ID: 157.0456 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0456)
    - "Candy Snatchers, Shot by SJ, Camera Mike 8/8/00", 2000; ID: 157.0458 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0458)
    - "My Apartment Willis Project 11/11/00", 2000; ID: 157.0461 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0461)
    - Lunachicks Videos, [1] "Say What You Mean" [2] "Naked", Undated; ID: 157.0462 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0462)
    - "Law + Order 10/2000, Gorilla Girls", ID: 157.0464 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0464)
    - "Le Tigre, Law + Order 10/00", 2000; ID: 157.0465 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0465)
    - "Riot Headline", Undated; ID: 157.0466 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0466)
    - "Rosewood Poetry Reading [No Sound]", Undated; ID: 157.0467 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0467)
    - "Ali's Apt Rap Flashdance", Undated; ID: 157.0468 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0468)
    - "Arin + Her Friends: In Her Room, Phone Chat, Boys, Mall, Town, Porto's Pizza, Delaware City 11/99", 1999; ID: 157.0469 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0469)
    - "In SF Before Moving: [1] Selling Books [2] Car Wash [3] Garage Sale [4] Christian Film Cafe [5] Jack Stevenson at LaRondella [6] Bank Deposit [7] Greg in Union Sq. [8] Haircut - Timecode Break [9] Learning Annex Class [10] AIDS Test [11] MAC - Buying Make-Up [12] SF Beach [13] Canyon Cinema [14] Sunny's Office [15] Gillman MJ Show", Undated; ID: 157.0470 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0470)
    - "SF, etc: [1] MAX [2] On the Bus [3] Swing Dancing [4] Punk Basketball [5] Willie Brown 10/99", 1999; ID: 157.0471 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0471)
    - "Me + Tony at CBGBs 4/27/2001", ID: 157.0472 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0472)
    - "Moving from Sublet to 347, Editing Fiasco, Mom in NY / Sublet, Manhattan Mini, New Movie, Cable Eric, Eric's a Dick, Feel Better, Bossitogg Drill, New Storage, Hitairi, Mama Said, New Studio, 12/2-17/99", 1999; ID: 157.0473 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0473)
    - "Lori's House, Kristin T., 8/99", 1999; ID: 157.0474 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0474)
    - "Sunny + Kevin's Wedding, Liz Shoots Clone Other * People 9/99", 1999; ID: 157.0475 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0475)
    - "Private Projections by Brian Chang [Blank]", Undated; ID: 157.0476 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0476)
    - "Barefoot Cont. [Blank]", Undated; ID: 157.0477 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0477)
    - "C.B.D. 006 [Blank]", Undated; ID: 157.0478 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0478)
    - "BBW 005", Undated; ID: 157.0479 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0479)
    - "Hospice Interview 1/29/04", 2004; ID: 157.0500 (Box 30, Media ID: 157.0500)
      Notation inside original housing indicates that Sarah did this interview two weeks before she died.
      Format: DVD, Donated Element
  - Subseries E: Computer Discs
    This subseries includes floppy discs. Notation on original housing indicates that Sarah wrote Popcorn and later Mary Jane drafts on this format, between 1990-1991 at Bard College.
    - Appleworks Preboot v2.0, 1990-1991 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0001)
      Format: Scotch Floppy Disk, Donated Element
    - Appleworks Program v2.0, 1990-1991 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0002)
    - Unidentified BASF Diskette, 1990-1991 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0003)
      Format: BASF Diskette, Donated Element
    - Unidentified Kodak Diskette, 1990-1991 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0004)
      Format: Kodak Diskette, Donated Element
    - "Interactive Systems, Inc.," Scotch Diskette, 1990-1991 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0005)
    - Data Disk II, 1990-1991 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0006)
      Format: Irish Floppy Disk, Donated Element
    - Data Disk No. 3, 1990-1991 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0007)
      Format: Irish Floppy Disk in Kodak Diskette Sleeve, Donated Element
    - "Free", 1990-1991 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0008)
      Format: Irish Floppy Disc in Scotch Diskette Sleeve, Donated Element
    - 2nd Copy, Chap. 1, 2, 3 Improved, 1990-1991 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0009)
      Format: BASF Floppy Disc in Kodak Diskette Sleeve, Donated Element
    - 2nd Copy Chap. 4, 5, 1990-1991 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0010)
      Format: BASF Floppy Disc, Donated Element
    - 2nd Copy, Chap. 6, 7, 1990-1991 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0011)
    - 2nd Copy, Chap. 8,9, 1990-1991 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0012)
    - 2nd Copy, Chap 10, 11, 1990-1991 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0013)
      Format: Floppy Disc, Donated Element
    - Early Writings 1980s (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0014)
      Format: TDK Disc, Donated Element
    - Early Writings Bard 1989-92, 1989-1992 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0015)
    - Writing 1995-1999 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0016)
    - From Computer 1, 2004 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0017)
    - Mary Jane, From Computer 2, 2004 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0018)
    - From Computer 3, 2004 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0019)
    - From Computer 4, 2004 (Box 31, Disk ID: 157.3.0020)
- Accretion 2008 - Series VII: Printed Material, 1990-2004
  - Assorted Published Clips, 1990-2002 (Box 21, Folder 159)
  - Homage and Obituary Press about Sarah G. Jacobson, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 160)
  - It's Your World - If You Don't Like It, Change It, Activism for Teenagers by Mikki Halpin, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 233)
    General Note
    Includes an inscription from the author.
  - Chris Gore's Ultimate Film Festival Survival Guide, 3rd Edition, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 234)
  - Girl Director by Andrea Richards, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 235)
    Includes a dedication to Jacobson.
  - Microfilm, The Magazine of Personal Cinema in Action #7, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 236)
  - SPIN Magazine, March 2002 (Box 23, Folder 237)
  - RAYGUN Magazine, #71 September 1999 (Box 23, Folder 238)
  - JANE Magazine, December 2001 (Box 23, Folder 239)
  - Time Out New York, Issue 437, February 12-19, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 240)
  - Maximum Rock 'n Roll, # 252, May 2004 (Box 23, Folder 241)
  - BUST Magazine, Summer 2004 (Box 23, Folder 242)
  - Venus Zine, Issue # 11, Winter 2001 (Box 23, Folder 243)
- Accretion 2008 - Series VIII: Teaching Materials, 2001-2003
  - College Lecture Files, 2001-2003 (Box 21, Folder 161)
  - Teaching Annex Advertisement, Undated (Box 21, Folder 162)
- Accretion 2008 - Series X: Miscellaneous, 1984-2004
  - Subseries A: Assorted Personal Items, 1984-2002
    - "Bat Mitzvah Stuff", 1984 (Box 21, Folder 163)
    - Ticket Stubs and Programs, 1988-2001 (Box 21, Folder 164)
    - Season's Greetings Calendar, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 166)
    - Calvin and Hobbes 16-Month Calendar, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 167)
    - Charles Burns Calendar, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 168)
    - San Francisco Underground Bands Calendar, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 169)
    - The Wagons of Steel Calendar, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 170)
    - The WRS Calendar, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 172)
    - Skid Row A Go-Go Game, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 173)
    - Palm Pilot Manual and Correspondence, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 174)
    - NYC Maps, 2000-2002 (Box 21, Folder 175)
    - Personal Basic Principles, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 176)
    - Feng Shui House Plans, Undated (Box 21, Folder 177)
    - "Made a searching and fearless moral inventoy of ourselves", Undated (Box 21, Folder 178)
    - Assorted Blank Postcards, Undated (Box 21, Folder 179)
    - Assorted Ephemera, Undated (Box 21, Folder 180)
    - "Sarah's Video Cassette Chart", Undated (Box 21, Folder 182)
    - Assorted Photographs and Negatives, Undated (Box 21, Folder 183)
  - Subseries B: Personal Correspondence, 1981-2004
    - Personal Correspondence 1, 1981-1987 (Box 21, Folder 184)
    - Personal Correspondence 2, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 185)
    - Personal Correspondence 3, 1990-1993 (Box 21, Folder 186)
    - Personal Correspondence 4, 1994-1999 (Box 21, Folder 187)
    - Personal Correspondence 5, 2000-2004 (Box 21, Folder 188)
  - Subseries C: Objects, Undated
    - Car Accident Latex Bracelet, Undated (Box 23, Object ID: 157.2.0049)
    - White Axcess Pouch with Assorted Pins, Undated (Box 23, Object ID: 157.2.0050)
    - Peanuts Lunch Box, Undated (Box 23, Object ID: 157.2.0051)
    - Flower Coaster, Undated (Box 23, Object ID: 157.2.0052)
      This item was originally found among the Smiley Face Collection.
- Accretion 2008 - Series XII: Student Materials, 1976-1993
  - Subseries A: Elementary School - High School Documents, 1976-1989
    - Report Cards, 1976-1989 (Box 22, Folder 189)
    - Standardized Test Reports, 1979-1989 (Box 22, Folder 190)
    - Awards and Certificates, 1981-1989 (Box 22, Folder 191)
    - "A Bent Rainbow in Oz" by Sarah Jacobson, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 192)
    - Music Notebook, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 193)
    - Writing Files, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 194)
    - Gifted Community College Program, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 195)
    - Music Notebook, "Original Songs", 1985 (Box 22, Folder 196)
    - Creative Writing Class Assignments, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 197)
    - Creative Writing Files, 1986-1988 (Box 22, Folder 198)
    - NFTY In Israel Bulletin #3, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 199)
    - Sketch Diary, Undated (Box 22, Folder 202)
    - High School Class Photo, Undated (Box 22, Folder 203)
    - Notebook, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 204)
    - Sheet Music and Original Lyrics, Undated (Box 22, Folder 205)
    - Music Notebook, Undated (Box 22, Folder 206)
    - High School Writing, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 207)
    - Cinema Arts Class Materials and Assignments, Undated (Box 22, Folder 208)
    - Notebook, "Film Notes", 1988 (Box 22, Folder 209)
    - "Franklin High School" Story by Sarah Jacobson, Undated (Box 22, Folder 210)
  - Subseries B: Collegiate Documents, 1989-1993
    - Bard College, Schoolwork and Application Materials, 1989-1992 (Box 22, Folder 211)
    - Bard College, Report Cards & Application Materials, 1989-1991 (Box 22, Folder 212)
    - Sarah's Going Away Party Flyer, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 213)
    - Bard College, Student ID Card, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 214)
    - Bard College, Creative Writing, Scripts, and Flyers, 1989-1991 (Box 22, Folder 215)
    - Bard College, Art History Notebook, 1989-1991 (Box 22, Folder 216)
    - Bard College, Notebook, 1989-1991 (Box 22, Folder 217)
    - Bard College, Notebook, 1989-1991 (Box 22, Folder 218)
    - Bard College, Notebook, 1989-1991 (Box 22, Folder 219)
    - Bard College, Notebook, 1989-1991 (Box 22, Folder 220)
    - Date Log Book, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 221)
    - Address Book, Notebook, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 222)
    - Bard College Film Committee Materials, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 223)
    - "Sarah's Life in 366 Simple Days" Pocket Diary, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 224)
    - SF Art Institute, "This Is Stuff In My Notebook!" Notebook, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 225)
    - Beverly Hills, 90210 Special 1992-93 Student Planner, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 226)
    - SF Art Institute, Notebook, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 227)
    - SF Art Institute, "Art School Chicks" Contact Sheets and Storyboard, 1992-1994 (Box 22, Folder 228A)
    - SF Art Institute, "History of Cinema" Notebook, 1992-1994 (Box 23, Folder 229)
    - Notebook, Undated (Box 23, Folder 231)
    - New School University, "Acting for Filmmakers" Student Materials, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 232)
  - Subseries C: Photographs, Undated
    - SF Art Institute Photographs, 1992-1994 (Album 32)
- Accretion 2008 - Oversize Series IV: Professional Projects
  - Subseries B: Sleaze
    - "Chicks in Rock" Collected Press Clips, 1980-2002 (Box 24, Folder 73B)
- Accretion 2008 - Oversize Series X: Miscellaneous
  - Subseries A: Assorted Personal Items
    - James Dean Calendar, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 165)
    - At A Glance Calendar, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 171)
    - Assorted Posters and Flyers, Undated (Box 24, Folder 181)
- Accretion 2008 - Oversize Series XII: Student Materials
  - Subseries A: Elementary - High School Documents
    - "Sarah in Israel," Sketch Diary, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 200)
    - Sketchpad, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 201)
  - Subseries B: Collegiate Documents
    - SF Art Institute, "Art School Chicks" Contact Sheets, 1992-1994 (Box 24, Folder 228B)
    - SF Art Institute, Chicago International Film Festival Certificate of Merit for I Was A Teenage Serial Killer, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 230)
- Series XIII: 2018 Accretion, 1953-2012; 14 VHS; 17 DVDs; 30 MiniDV; 7 CDs; 4 DAT; 1 audiocassette; 1 Half_Inch_Video_Reel; 4.22 Gigabytes in 6057 computer files
  Arrangement